A Guide to the Records of the Office of the President, Walter S. Newman, 1947-1962 (Bulk 1947-1961)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series I. General Correspondence, 1947-1961
  - General Correspondence, 1954
    - English and Foreign Language Department, M.C. Harrison, Head (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Extension Division (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Farrier, P.H., Director of Admissions (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Glee Club, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Governor of Virginia (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Guthridge, J.W., Director of Civilian Students (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Harrison, E.D., Assistant Dean of Engineering (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Hart, Harris, State Director of Personnel (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Home Economics Department, Dr. Mildred T. Tate, Head (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., Chancellor (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Industrial Engineering Department, H.L. Manning, Head (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Insurance, Group (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - J, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - L, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and Universities (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Legislation (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Military College Presidents (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Military Department (Box 9, Folder 53-54)
    - N, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - O, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - P, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Panty Raid (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Pardue, L.A., Director of Graduate Studies (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Pardue, L.A., Vice President (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Physics Department (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Plant Pathology Department (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - President's Council (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - R, miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Radford College (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Research Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute; E.B. Norris, Director (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Salary Schedule (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Southern Athletic Conference (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Southern Conference Presidents (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - State Department of Agriculture (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - State Department of Education (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - State Department of Education, General Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 17-19)
    - Statistics - Summer Conference (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Student Inquiries from Parents, etc. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Student Organizations (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Students - General Letters to and from (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Summer Conferences (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Swink, H.W., Purchasing and Personnel (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - T, miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - U, miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - V, miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Vandenburg, H.P.C., Institutional Engineer (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Virginia State Board of Agriculture (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Wills and Endowments (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Whittemore, J.W., Dean of Engineering (Box 10, Folder 38-40)
    - Young, H.N. (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence, 1955
    - A, miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Abbitt, J.R. (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Accrediting, National Committee on; Engineers Council on Professional Development (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Agricultural:Vocational Education Department (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology Department (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Agricultural Engineering Department, E.T. Swink, Head (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Agronomy Department, Dr. H.L. Dunton, Head (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Alumni Association, Fund Council (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Alumni Association, General (Box 10, Folder 51-52)
    - Alumni Association, President's Emergency Fund (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - American Council on Education (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Animal Husbandry Department (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Applications for Positions (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Applied Mechanics Department (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Architectural Department (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Association of American Universities (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Association of Virginia Colleges (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Council (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Attorney General J. Lindsay Almond (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Audits (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - B, miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Biology Department (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Bradford, J.H. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Budget Matters (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Business Administration Department (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - C, miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Capital Outlay Needs (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Cadet Corps (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Cassell, S.K. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Cato, W.H. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Chemical Engineering Department (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Chemistry Department (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Civil Engineering Department (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Civilian Student Body (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Commandant of Cadets (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Commencement Exercises, Requests to be Excused (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Consultative Work for Faculty (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Dietrick, L.B., Dean of Agriculture (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Dining Hall (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 11, Folder 36-38)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Scholarships (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Evans, E.B., Personnel (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Faculty Lists (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Farrier, P.H. (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Geology Department (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Governor of Virginia, Thomas B. Stanley (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Guthridge, J.W., Director, Civilian Students (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - H, miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Hardy, J.E., Manager of Dormitories (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Hart, Harris, Director of Personnel (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Harrison, Dr. E.D., Assistant Dean of Engineering (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Home Economics Department (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - J, miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - L, miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, Association of (Box 11, Folder 55-56)
    - Legislation (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - McNeil, R.H., Publications (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Military Department (Box 12, Folder 2-4)
    - Pardue, L.A., Vice-President (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pardue, L.A., Director of Graduate Studies (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Physics Department (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Plant Pathology Department (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - President's Council (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Radford College (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Salary Schedule (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, Loans (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Southern Athletic Conference (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Southern Conference Presidents (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
    - State Board of Education, General Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Statistics Department (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Student Organizations (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Summer Conferences (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce and Civil Defense (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Box 12, Folder 26-28)
    - Virginia State Board of Agriculture (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Whittemore, J.W., Dean of Engineering (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Wills (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Young, H.N., Director of Virginia Agricultural Extension Service (Box 12, Folder 33-24)
    - Younger, W.L. (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - YMCA (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - General Correspondence, 1956
    - Accrediting, National Commission on; Engineers Council on Professional Development (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Agricultural Engineering Department, Seitz Hall Dedication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Agricultural:Vocational Education Department (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Alumni Association Fund Council (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Alumni Association, General (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Applied Mechanics Department (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Architectural Department (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Attorney General J. Lindsay Almond (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Audit (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Biology Department (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Bradford, J.H. (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Budget Matters (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Business Administration Department (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Capital Outlay Needs (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Cato, W.H., Director, Guidance and Placement (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Commandant of Cadets (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Council of Higher Education (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Dietrick, Dean L.B., Agriculture (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - English and Foreign Language (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Lists (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Farrier, Dr. P.H. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Governor of Virginia, Thomas B. Stanley (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Guthridge, J.W., Director of Civilian Student Affairs (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Horticulture Department (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - J, miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Johnston, G. Burke, Dean of Academic Science and Business Administration (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Military Department (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Pardue, Louis A., Vice-President (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Personnel (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Physics Department (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - President's Council (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Radford College (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1957
    - State Department of Education, Granville P. Meade Scholarships (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Statistics Department (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Student Housing (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Student Organizations (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - A, miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Accrediting, National Commission on; Engineers Council on Professional Development (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Agricultural:Vocational Education Department (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Alumni Association Fund Council (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Alumni Association, General (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Applied Mechanics Department (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Architectural Department (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Association of Virginia Colleges (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Attorney General (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Budget Matters (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Business Administration Department (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Carpenter, Hunter (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Cassell, S.K., Business Manager (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Cato, Dr. W.H. (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Commandant of Cadets (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Council of Higher Education (Box 13, Folder 43-44)
    - Cregger, S.G., Auditor (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - D, miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Dairy Science Department (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Daughtrey, W.H. (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Dietrick, L.B., Dean of Agriculture (Box 13, Folder 49-50)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 13, Folder 51-52)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Scholarships (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Faculty Lists (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Fuller, Dr. L.E., Director, Admissions (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Governor of Virginia, Thomas B. Stanley (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Guthridge, J.W. (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Hart, Dr. Harris (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Homecoming Committee (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Home Economics Department (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Johnston, D. Burke, Dean Academic Science and Business Administration (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, Association of (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Legislation (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Library (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - McNeil, R.H., Publications (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Military Department, Colonel W.J. Daniel (Box 13, Folder 68-69)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Pardue, Dr. Louis A., Vice-President (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Personnel, E.B. Evans, Director (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Physics Department (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - President's Council (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - R, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Radford College (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Salary Schedules (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Salary Schedules, New (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Southern Conference (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - State Board of Education (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - State Board of Education, G.P. Meade Scholarships (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Statistics Department (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Student Joint Committee (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Student Organizations (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Summer Conferences (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Swink, H.W. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - T, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Television (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - U, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - V, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Board (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Virginia State Board of Agriculture (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - W, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Whittemore, Dr. J.W. (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - YMCA (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Young, Dr. H.N. (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    - XYZ, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence, 1958
    - A, miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Academic Council (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Accrediting, National Commission on, and Engineers Professional Council on Development (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Alumni Association, General; H.B. Redd, Secretary (Box 14, Folder 37-39)
    - Applied Mechanics Department, Professor D.H. Pletta, Head (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Architectural Department, Dr. L.J. Currie, Head (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Association of Virginia Colleges (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Auditor, S.G. Cregger (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - B, miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Biochemistry and Nutrition, Dr. R.W. Engle, Head (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Biology Department (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Bradford, J.H., Director of State Budget (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Business Manager, S.K. Cassell (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Budget Matters (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Cadet Corps (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Commandant of Cadets, General J.M. Devine (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Commencement, Committee on (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Council of Higher Education, Dr. P.H. Farrier, Executive Secretary (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
    - Cultural and Social Program Committee (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Department of Development; Employment of Earl Fisher, Youngberg and McCarthy Survey of Development (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Development, Director of, Earl Fisher (Box 15, Folder 20-21)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Governor of Virginia, Judge Lindsay Almond (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Graduate Student Body (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Home Economics Department, Dr. Mildred T. Tate, Head (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Honors Day Convocation (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - J, miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Joint Institutional Research (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, Association of (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Legislation (Box 15, Folder 32-33)
    - Library, Annual Report, Seymour Robb, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - McNeil, R.H., Director, Publicity (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Military College (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Physics Department (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - President's Council (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Radford College (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Religious Activities (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Salary Schedules (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Southern Conference (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
    - State Board of Education (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Technical Institutes (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Television (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Board (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Virginia State Board of Agriculture (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Whittemore, J.W., Dean (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - YMCA (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Young, Dr. H.N. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1959
    - A, miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Academic Council (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Accrediting, National Committee on, Engineers Council on Professional Development (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Admissions, Director of, Dr. Paul H. Farrier; Dr. Landon E. Fuller, Associate (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Aeronautical Engineering, Dr. R.W. Truitt, Head (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology, Dr. H.M. Love, Head (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Agricultural Education (Vocational Education, Business Education); Professor H.W. Swink, Head (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Agronomy Department, Dr. H.L. Dunton, Head (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Association, General, H.B. Redd, Secretary-Treasurer (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Citations (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - American Council on Education (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Animal Husbandry Department, Professor G.W. Litton, Head (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Applied Mechanics Department, Professor D.H. Pletta (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Architectural Department, Dr. L.J. Currie, Head (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Architecture, National Accrediting Board (NAAB) (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Attorney General, Honorable A.S. Harrison, Jr. (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Auditor, S.G. Cregger (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - B, miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Biochemistry and Nutrition, Dr. R.W. Engel, Head (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Biology Department (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Budget, Director of; L.M. Kuhn (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Budget Matters (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Buildings and Grounds (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Business Administration Department (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Business Manager, S.K. Cassell (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, Dr. F.W. Bull, Head (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Chemistry Department, R.C. Krug, Head (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Commandant of Cadets, General J.M. Devine (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Council of Higher Education (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Dairy Science Department, Dr. G.C. Graf, Head (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Daughtrey, W.H., Director of Extension (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Development Program, Earl Fisher, Director (Box 16, Folder 50-52)
    - Dietrick, Dean L.B., Agriculture (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Dining Hall, H.P. King, Director (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Entomology Department, Dr. J.M. Grayson, Head (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Extension, General and Branches: Danville, Norfolk, Bluefield (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Forestry, Wildlife, and Conservation; Dr. H.S. Mosby, Jr.; J.J. Aulbach, C.J. Holcomb, Rotating Heads (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - Geological Sciences, Dr. B.N. Cooper, Head (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Governor of Virginia, J. Lindsay Almond (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Guidance and Placement, Dr. W.H. Cato, Director (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Home Economics Department, Dr. L.J. Harper, Head (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
    - Homecoming Committee (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Johnston, G. Burke, Dean of School of Academic Science and Business Administration (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Legislation (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
    - Library (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Lund, Donald Hugo, Student Affairs (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Mathematics Department, Dr. T.W. Hatcher (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Military Department, Colonel E.H. Thompson, Army; Colonel R.F. Ireland, Air Force (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - N, miscellaneous; National Science Foundation (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Pardue, Dr. Louis A., Vice-President and Director of Graduate Studies (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Personnel, Director of (Dr. J.W. Garber, Richmond office) (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Physics Department, Dr. T.M. Hahn, Jr., Head (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Plant Pathology Department, Dr. S.A. Wingard, Head (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - President's Council (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Radford College, Dr. C.K. Martin, Jr., President (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Registrar, Miss Clarice Slusher (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Religious Activities, P.N. Derring, Director (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Salary Schedule (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 17, Folder 35-36)
    - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities (Box 17, Folder 37-38)
    - Southern Athletic Council (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Statistics Department, Dr. Boyd Harshbarger, Head (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Student Affairs, Dr. J.W. Dean, Director and Dean of Civilian Students (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Student Joint Committee (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Technical Institutes (Box 17, Folder 44)